Like most of us, your life has probably changed dramatically
in the last few years.
Every day you rely on digital devices, technologies, and services
that didn't exist just a few years ago.
The way we work has changed too.
The most successful organizations today are highly digital, nimble,
relentlessly finding new ways to create value
for customers and consumers, employees, and broader society.
What's the secret to their success?
It's not just technology.
It's the people who find new ways to use technology,
collect and analyze data, and collaborate with others.
Right now, farmers are growing more food
and feeding more people because of digital.
Large companies are perfecting complex systems
in supply chain, manufacturing and distribution,
to produce and deliver goods on a scale never before achieved.
Medical teams are finding more efficient ways to distribute
life-saving medicine and vaccines to hard-to-reach patients.
Design teams are inventing products and services
that will one day seem indispensable.
All of this is possible because of the people who saw a problem
and used data, technology, and new ways of working to solve it.
We can achieve new levels of success as well.
You, as an individual, play a pivotal role in forging our future.
Digital is bringing a future that will allow you
to better connect and collaborate with other people.
Changes in technology will allow you to focus
on the most inspiring and creative parts of your job.
New methods of collecting and analyzing data
will allow you to make faster and more accurate decisions.
New team structures and ways of working will allow you to innovate
and get more done with less effort, extending your reach and impact.
How will this future come about?
We are all inventing it. Together.
We make the future happen as we apply new technology, data, and ways of working
to better serve the people who rely on us.
We each contribute to our collective success if we stay curious,
take opportunities to learn new skills,
and if we continually seek new possibilities.